♪看来今天 你所看到的一切♪
♪电影中的暴力 和电视中的性爱♪
♪但那些好的老式价值观在哪里 ♪
♪我们曾经依赖什么？♪
♪幸运的是，有一个顾家的男人♪
♪幸运的是，有一个人 确实能做到♪
♪所有造就我们的事物♪
♪又笑又哭♪
♪他是……一个…… 家人……非常……的家伙。♪
[叹气]狗娘养的。
怎么了，彼得？
呃，我们的 IT 人员今天告诉我，显然，
自从我开始工作以来，我就有了一个工作电子邮件地址。
所以现在我必须艰难地处理 17,000 条消息。
哦，糟糕，我们不必在 9/11 进来吗？
我从来都不喜欢在那个愚蠢的啤酒厂工作。
这几乎不是我梦想的工作，我就告诉你这么多。
现在，有一个有趣的问题。
你梦想的工作是什么？
理想职业？哦，这很容易。
自从我还是个孩子的时候，
我一直把自己想象成一名国际间谍。
♪ ♪
那么，美丽的你拔掉了哪盏灯
在房间里给手机充电？
我的在浴室里。
嗯，你知道，我从来没听过你的名字。
名字叫乐队。膝带。
-[快速枪声]-[尖叫声]
小心。来自任何国家的坏人都来了
不会冒犯美国或中国观众。
-[枪声]-[咕哝声]
班德先生，你侮辱了芬兰人民。
开枪打死他吧，那些高个子内向的人。
[Marvin Hamlisch 演奏的《Bond 77》]
是的。全部肯定是我。
嗖嗖。飞涨。
滑雪噪音。
[Pilot 的“Magic”曲子] ♪哦，哦，Ozempic... ♪
他们向我们扔了很多钱。
我们不能说不。
【戏剧性、爵士乐主题演奏】
[彼得咯咯笑] 好吧。
嘿，我想知道他们是谁来 演唱这首歌。
床单。
♪当你是间谍时♪
♪你有很多想法♪
♪你看起来高高在上♪
♪你永远不知道 会发现什么♪
♪间谍生活。♪
[彼得叹气] 幸好简短。
早上好，特工 5-5-5。
呃，对。因为这是电视节目中的数字。
我说，你看起来还是一如既往的迷人，塔卡彭尼小姐。
哦，你没听到吗？我结婚了。
我现在是 Takeapenny-Leaveapenny 女士。
哇，幸运的先生。
因为他会犁你，这就是我的意思。
如此温文尔雅。
你知道，既然我已经结婚了，我实际上就要离开了。
我正在训练我的替补，托德。
男秘书？
[叹气]好吧，我想我必须适应
现在还骚扰他。
不错的阴茎，托德。
哦，班德先生。
好吧，很好，他知道如何配合。
是的，这是——这会起作用的。
我知道你对我有一个使命，M，
我只能假设它代表“男人”。
早上好，班德先生。
哇哦。我的老板是新的小美人鱼
我很生气。
班德先生，我们有一个计划的报告
拦截欧洲核装置
由邪恶的主谋布洛费拉所为。
明白了，M。
或者-或者可能是 MHM 而你发音为“mm-hmm”？
M 很好。
好吧，是的，我——时代变了
我必须——我需要赶上。
♪ ♪
哦，嘿，Q。嘿，你看到M是谁了吗？
顺便说一句，我完全支持。
事实上，这是我的想法，我也为之奋斗。
你应该听我说的。
好吧，让我给你展示一下最先进的设备
你需要完成你的使命。
首先，我有一台可以显示今日头条新闻的冰箱。
你刚刚去了百思买吗？
不，我也有这款耳机
阻挡环境平面噪音。
是的，你——你刚刚去了百思买。
-我没有！-那么，我要去哪里？
我们期待布洛费拉
试图在比利时拦截炸弹。
哦，太棒了。
这就是他们基本上拥有的国家
早餐的甜点，对吗？
特工三五，我怎么强调都不为过——
早餐没有甜点。
♪ ♪
您好，班德先生，
代表比利时特勤局。
噢！嗨。我会握你的手
但我的手臂被糖浆粘在了桌子上。
名字叫爱丽丝。爱丽丝胸部。
[咯咯笑]这有两种方式。
不，它——它真的只是一个。
♪ ♪
我们的情报显示炸弹转移是
在这个通用木箱仓库中进行。
♪ ♪
-[直升机大声呼呼]-[说话含糊不清]
什么？声音很大。
[含糊不清地喊叫]
我们什么也得不到。
如果我们听不到他的话
他听不到我们说我们听不到他的声音。
真是一团糟！
加文. 加文.
关闭——关闭直升机。
我想说，“很抱歉参加你的聚会，”
但是，呃，现在感觉很愚蠢。
抓住他们，孩子们。
就这样吧，布洛费拉？
你就想让我们被你的追随者杀死吗？
哦，好吧，我宁愿你不要用这个词。
他们是独立承包商。
他不想给我们福利。
他们想工作时会登录一个应用程序，
围绕他们的日程安排。
我不是他们的雇主。该应用程序是他们的雇主。
再见，班德先生。
[疯狂地笑]
[咕噜声]
[呻吟]
[彼得] 看起来不太好。
但值得庆幸的是， Q 为我提供了......
美国队长的盾牌。
[泥潭] 什么？不不不。
你不能只是成为
一个漫威角色 已经看到一半了。
[Joe] 另外，我们通常会看到 所有的东西
Q 一开始就给你。
这让人感觉非常不劳而获。
[彼得] 比利时情报部门获悉 布洛费拉的计划是
使用 他拦截的核装置
炸毁 拉斯维加斯市。
但这并不是 我要处理的唯一紧急情况。
是的，你说维加斯的每个人都穿着燕尾服，
我开始感到很不自在。
呃，我没有说“肯定”。
我说：“这是我的理解。”
[喘气]特工三五，看。
[欢呼]
[喘气]布洛费拉。不在我的监视之下。
-[咕哝声] -[尖叫声]
[老虎机鸣响]
[疲惫的喘息]
我找不到出路。
好的，好吧，就是这样说的“自助早餐”，
但我很确定我们已经看过两次了。
♪ ♪
我们又来到了北套房电梯。
我不知道，我们是否应该——我们应该只是
我们在这里玩老虎机吗？
不，这就是他们这样做的原因。
不，不，是的，不，我明白了，
我讨厌拖延事情，但是...
我是说，桑塔纳已经 70 多岁了。
我们也许应该趁还能见到他的时候。
呃。
【吉他独奏】
[彼得] 我知道一首歌。
[吉他独奏结束]
王八蛋。
♪ ♪
我们到了。组装完成。
所以，再一次，这将是一个合适的时间
请大家退出该应用程序。
-[乐队]哈！我明白你了现在。-[喘气]
班德先生。你是怎么找到我的？
老实说，我正在参加电影《宿醉》的导游，
结束于屋顶。
有趣的是，伙计们——这实际上是扎克的主意
给宝宝戴上太阳镜。
好吧，我看到大家都盯着曼德勒湾，
所以我会继续告诉你哪个窗户是枪手的。
好吧，你太晚了。
过不了多久，整个拉斯维加斯都会
完全从地图上消失了。
[咕噜声]
你是个疯子。你为什么做这个？
我需要摆脱一项非常严格的分时度假协议
这确实是唯一的出路。
♪ ♪
[彼得] 没有时间了。
于是我就拿出了 凯洛·伦的光剑
并将布洛费拉 从屋顶上撞下来。
[尖叫声]
[泥潭] 不，不，不，不。那是作弊。
[乔] 还有，你有一把光剑，
你就想 推一个人吗？
[砰]
哦，三五，你救了我的命。
现在就和我做爱吧。
对不起，爱丽丝，我不能。我是同性恋。
新邦德。编辑为雪花。
♪ ♪
哇，听到你梦想的工作真是太棒了，彼得。
但实际上我很幸运能够拥有我梦想的工作。
至少在我失去它之前是这样。
这一切都始于几年前。
那是20世纪80年代， 我一个人住
在一张斜海报的单间公寓里
因为单身汉从来不会把 海报挂直。
[Peter] 是的，无意冒犯，Quagmire，
但我要听 这个故事
就像我做 大多数播客一样——
以 1.5 的速度。
[泥潭，加速] 我会增加一些体重
与一名女性处于虐待关系中——
-塞莱斯特妈妈。 -丰富。
[彼得] 好吧，好吧。 Ba-恢复正常速度。
我进来了。我着迷了。
[泥潭] 生活在 80 年代的另一件事 是，
无论你走到哪里，真正的指针姐妹
会跟着你到处唱歌。
[“跳跃（为了我的爱）”的曲调] ♪格伦♪
♪你知道这个人 刚刚寄了一张账单♪
♪冲刺♪
♪这是给他的手机的♪
♪固定电话。♪
[泥潭] 我知道我需要 保持身材，
但80 年代唯一的锻炼形式是
在舞池上滑旱冰
或者拖着死去的老板 去使用他的度假屋。
那时， 我喜欢两件事：
旋转我的骨盆
并将元音放在 一起
通常情况下，它们并不 相邻。
我把这两种爱结合在一起
创造一种叫做 “有氧运动”的东西。
欢迎登机。
这是您的免费头带，
两个腕带、腰带、大腿带、另一个头带。
有很多乐队。
[Peter] 是的，我的手指悬停 在那个 1.5 按钮上。
[泥潭] 好吧，好吧，好吧。
所以我在同一周开始上课。
我什至创建了一个高级课程
基于您 在性爱过程中身体的移动方式。
我称之为“性锻炼”。
♪ ♪
事情立即开始了
因为我给了 20 世纪 80 年代女性 她们想要的东西：
又长又平的屁股。
来吧，女士们。更长！奉承！
我的锻炼计划很成功
很快我就准备好 将其推向全国。
我很幸运 有机会宣布
我在《约翰尼 今夜秀》中拍摄的视频。
[乔] 哇！你见过约翰尼·卡森吗？
[泥潭] 其实那天晚上 还有一位嘉宾主持人，
约翰·戴维森， 《不可思议！》的主演。
所以，你知道，不同的约翰尼 ，但仍然是约翰尼。
[彼得] 从来没有人称 约翰·戴维森为“约翰尼”。
[泥潭] 他客串主持了87次。 那不是什么。
无论如何，当晚的第一位客人 是简·方达，
谁在提倡朝九晚五，
迄今为止 20 世纪 80 年代最精彩的电影。
那么，格伦·奎格米尔。
它说你在这里创建了
一种称为“有氧运动”的运动热潮
- 是什么启发了这个？-嗯，约翰...纽约，
有一天，当我独自在公寓里做开合跳时，
我想：“我怎样才能承受这一切中最糟糕的部分？
“然后把它放在公共场合？
加上一面镜子墙和临街的窗户。”
面试似乎 进行得很顺利。
但第二天，
我意识到简·方达是多么无情 。
♪ ♪
现在，Quagmire先生，发布1980年代视频的重要组成部分
是它开头令人难以置信的令人沮丧的生产标志。
我这里有几个可供选择。
首先是一些振动彩虹文本
这永远不会成为人们关注的焦点。
[不祥的合成音乐播放]
嗯嗯，喜欢这个
这只是一个弹跳的大“V”
伴随着不祥的键盘噪音。
[不祥的合成音乐播放]
也很优秀。
或者这是三个大写字母
全部用一根粗的连续线拼写
数字地平线之上。
[不祥的合成音乐播放]
哇，你不能错过。我们三个一起去吧。
等一下。什么事——发生什么事了？
我的暖腿器在哪里？
那时候， 暖腿是必不可少的
因为到目前为止，
从膝盖以下最冷的十年。
有人拿走了我的暖腿套吗？
我只找到一张纸条代替我的暖腿套。
起初，我以为
朱迪·福斯特偷了 我的暖腿裤
我正准备去向 总统出气。
但后来我意识到这可能 只是一个人的意图
破坏我——简·方达。
我尽力坚持下去。
好吧，别看我的腿。
一、二……我的小腿又小又冷。
还有三、四……
但我知道，即使在那一刻，
这将是一场灾难。
[喘气]
我从来没有机会。
♪ ♪
[简·方达]你好，格伦。
抱歉你失败了，但是...[笑]就像他们说的，
在爱情和有氧运动中一切都是公平的。
WHO？谁说的？没有人。
天哪，现在我明白为什么每个人的种族主义叔叔都恨你了。
嗯，聊天很愉快，但是请原谅，
我得去游说我们的国家
关于清理我们在越南造成的混乱。
-[音频加快] -[彼得]抱歉，我继续 打了 8-X。
[泥沼] 不，你-你-你做了， 你做了正确的事，彼得。
[不祥的合成音乐播放]
♪ ♪
好吧，就梦想的工作而言，
我的职责一直是做你所做的事，乔，成为一名警察。
但是，你知道，距离退休还有一天，
因为你们都得到了这么好的福利待遇。
呵呵。嗯，我梦想的工作就是做我现在所做的事情
但就像一个松散的大炮式警察
谁不在乎自己是死是活
但绝对可以走路。
♪ ♪
[克利夫兰] 这是我工作的最后一天，
我刚刚清理了 最后一次办公室垃圾场
当我被叫到 主任办公室时。
早上好，先生。你想见我吗？
这是正确的。我们一直在追踪
臭名昭著的贩毒集团
这给洛杉矶带来了大量的可卡因
是的，可卡因多年来一直肆虐黑人社区。
是的，有一个白人女孩流了轻微的鼻血，
所以现在我想这是一件大事。
事实上，昨晚发生了一次巨大的半身像。
哇，多少钱？
请记住，我们测量可卡因——
没有别的——只有公斤。
-我不知道，80磅？-啊？
比如，36公斤。
我的天啊！这也太多斤了吧！
哦，我还给你分配了一个新的搭档。
但别担心，我知道你即将退休
想要一个稳定的局面，
所以我要给你介绍一个叫疯狂中士的人。
你好吗？我是一张疯狂的外卡
正如我现在唯一及时的鲻鱼所表明的那样。
唔。你穿得不像警探。
好吧，我知道我们会到处追捕坏人，
所以我穿了我拥有的最紧的牛仔裤。
嗨呀！嗨呀！
嘿，你为什么不来我的海滨拖车里呢
呃，讨论这个案子？
当然。它在哪里？
呃，不是在马里布——他们不允许——
但更北边的那些垃圾海滩之一，
远远超过月影，那是一个完美的地方
喝醉了并告诉所有该负责的人
对于世界上所有的战争。
♪ ♪
[克利夫兰] 我很快意识到我的新伙伴 有严重的问题。
他不在乎 自己做了什么危险的事情。
-[电话铃声] -喂？
您是通过“信用卡服务”打来的吗？
太好了，我会告诉你我的社会安全号码，
然后你告诉我它是否与你那里的相符。
男人是疯了。
好吧，呃，别笑我母亲的娘家姓氏。
这是一种愚蠢的行为。
廷克曼。[笑]是的。就像……就像撒尿一样。
我以为我们要讨论这个案子
正确的。我会在一分钟内准备好 但首先
我被要求确保女性也来看这部电影。
♪ ♪
[克利夫兰] 所以我和我疯狂的搭档 开始解决这个案子
并开始寻找利兹，
这是一家颇受欢迎的 床垫商店，
如果您说您是 潜在客户，
他们会让你在中午小睡一会儿。
-[打鼾] -对不起，伙计们。
我的经理说你必须离开。
离开？但我和我的伴侣正在尝试这张大床。
-[咯咯笑]-你咯咯笑什么？
我们是警察部队的合作伙伴。
这家伙穿着牛仔裤，没有穿内裤。
是的，你们是警察。当然。
♪ ♪
你们还没有更接近弄清楚
谁负责带进所有这些可卡因
我有一个很好的主意。
您检查过布伦特伍德的以色列沙洛姆神庙吗？
这也是他们控制天气和奥斯卡的地方。
就是这样。你们已经脱离案子了。
♪ ♪
[克利夫兰] 自从我们被排除在 这个案子之外
我认为邀请我的伴侣过来会很好
- 一顿家常饭菜。 -嗯。
你没有一壶冰茶吗？
我以为每个黑人家庭的晚餐
喝了一壶冰茶。
我们确实有一张 Ice-T 的照片，
就在墙上。
[调度员] 各单位请注意
码头上可能发生的毒品交易
那离这里不远。
决不。我们被从那个案子中除名了。
是的，但我们甚至可以在最近的巡逻车之前到达那里。
♪ ♪
在那里，看。快点，靠边停车，让我出去。
-什么？-剩下的路我会跑完。
我向你保证这辆车会更快。
到时候那里见。
♪ ♪
[咕哝]
[气喘吁吁，咕哝]
在这里等了六分钟。
好吧，好吧，好吧，六分钟一英里。
穿牛仔裤和不穿内裤也不错。
手套箱里有凡士林吗？
这是酋长。我勒个去？
[喊叫]
首领一直是主谋
一直以来都是可卡因贩毒集团的成员。
这也许可以解释为什么他总是在凌晨 3:00 给我打电话
和剧本创意。
[电话铃声]
[咕噜声]喂？
[卡特] 好吧，听我说。
这是《虎胆龙威》， 不过是在一栋大楼里。
《虎胆龙威》在一座大楼里。
嗯，我不知道。 来，听我看一下，
我们会找到答案的。
[通过电话播放 20 世纪福克斯的宣传曲]
[两人咕哝]
放弃。你们无论如何也不能逮捕我。
我有外交豁免权。
-你做？-依据什么？
是的，我是玛格丽塔维尔的公民。
我什至还拥有最近度假时戴的这顶帽子来证明这一点。
[咆哮]太糟糕了。
你的外交豁免权刚刚被撤销。
[呻吟]
该官员的行为虽然违法，
被一条活泼的线条所证明是合理的。电影结束了。
[不祥的合成音乐播放]
[Quagmire] 我也是 这个项目的制作人。
♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who
positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy. ♪
[sighs] Son of a bitch.
What's wrong, Peter?
Eh, our I.T. guy told me today
that, apparently,
I've had a work e-mail address
ever since I started there.
So now I got to slog
through 17,000 messages.
Aw, crap, we didn't have
to come in on 9/11?
I never even liked working
at that stupid brewery.
Hardly my dream job,
I'll tell you that much.
Now, there's
an interesting question.
What would be your dream job?
Dream job? Oh, that's easy.
Ever since I was a kid,
I always pictured myself
being an international spy.
♪ ♪
So, beautiful,
which lamp did you unplug
to charge your phone
in the room?
Mine's in the bathroom.
Mm, you know,
I never caught your name.
The name is Band. Lap Band.
-[rapid gunfire]
-[screams]
Careful. Here come the bad guys
from whatever country
won't offend American
or Chinese audiences.
-[gunfire]
-[grunts]
You have dishonored the people
of Finland, Mr. Band.
Shoot him,
fellow tall introverts.
["Bond 77" by Marvin Hamlisch
playing]
Yep. All definitely me.
Whoosh. Zoom.
Ski noise.
[to tune of Pilot's "Magic"]
♪ Oh, oh, Ozempic... ♪
They threw a ton of money at us.
We couldn't say no.
[dramatic, jazzy theme playing]
[Peter chuckling]
All right.
Hey, I wonder who they got
to do the song.
Blech.
♪ When you're a spy ♪
♪ You got a lot on your mind ♪
♪ You look high and low ♪
♪ You never know
what you'll find ♪
♪ Spy life. ♪
[Peter sighs]
Mercifully brief.
Good morning, Agent 5-5-5.
Ugh, right. 'Cause this is
a number on a television show.
I say, you look as bewitching
as ever, Miss Takeapenny.
Oh, didn't you hear?
I got married.
I'm now
Ms. Takeapenny-Leaveapenny.
Wow, lucky gentleman.
Because he gets to plow you,
is what I mean.
So debonair.
You know, now that I'm married,
I'm actually leaving.
I'm training
my replacement, Todd.
A male secretary?
[sighs] Well, I suppose
I'll just have to adapt
and harass him now.
Nice penis, Todd.
Oh, Mr. Band.
Okay, good,
he knows how to play along.
Yeah, this is-- this'll work.
I understand you have
a mission for me, M,
which I can only assume
stands for "man."
Good morning, Mr. Band.
Whoa. My boss is
the new Little Mermaid
I'm so mad about.
Mr. Band, we have
reports of a plan
to intercept a European
nuclear device
by the villainous
mastermind, Blofella.
Got it, M.
Or-or is it maybe MHM
and you pronounce it "mm-hmm"?
M is fine.
Okay, yeah, I--
times have changed
and I-I got to--
I need to catch up.
♪ ♪
Oh, hey, Q.
Hey, have you seen who M is?
Which I totally support,
by the way.
In fact, it was my idea
and I fought for it.
You should've heard me.
Okay, just let me show you
the cutting-edge equipment
you'll need for your mission.
First, I have this fridge
that displays today's headlines.
Did-- did you just go
to Best Buy?
No. I also have these headphones
that block out
ambient plane noise.
Yeah, you-you just went
to Best Buy.
-I did not!
-So, where am I headed?
We're expecting Blofella
to attempt to intercept
the bomb in Belgium.
Oh, awesome.
That's the country where
they basically have
dessert for breakfast, right?
Agent triple-five,
I cannot stress enough--
no dessert for breakfast.
♪ ♪
Greetings, Mr. Band,
on behalf of Belgian
Secret Services.
Oh, hey.
I-I'd shake your hand,
but my arm is syrup-glued
to the table.
The name is Alice. Alice Boobs.
[giggles]
That works in two ways.
No, it's-it's really just one.
♪ ♪
Our intelligence has revealed
that the bomb transfer is
to take place in this warehouse
for generic wooden crates.
♪ ♪
-[helicopter whirring loudly]
-[speaking indistinctly]
What? It's very loud.
[shouting indistinctly]
We're getting none of this.
If we can't hear him,
he can't hear us saying
we can't hear him.
What a mess!
Gavin. Gavin.
Turn off--
turn the helicopter off.
I-I was going to say, "Sorry
to drop in on your party,"
but, uh, feels stupid now.
Get 'em, boys.
So that's it, Blofella?
You're just gonna have us
killed by your henchmen?
Oh, okay, I'd rather you
not use that word.
They are independent
contractors.
He doesn't want
to pay us benefits.
There is an app they log into
when they want to work,
around their schedule.
I am not their employer.
The app is their employer.
Goodbye, Mr. Band.
[laughing maniacally]
[grunting]
[groans]
[Peter]
It wasn't looking good.
But thankfully,
Q had supplied me with...
Captain America's shield.
[Quagmire]
What? No, no, no.
You can't just become
a Marvel character
halfway through.
[Joe]
Also, we usually see
all the stuff
Q gives you at the beginning.
This feels very unearned.
[Peter]
Belgian intelligence learned
that Blofella's plan was
to use the nuclear device
he'd intercepted
to blow up the city
of Las Vegas.
But that wasn't the only
emergency I was dealing with.
Yeah, you said everyone
in Vegas wears tuxedos,
and I'm starting to feel
pretty self-conscious.
Uh, I didn't say "definitely."
I said,
"It was my understanding."
[gasps]
Agent triple-five, look.
[cheering]
[gasps]
Blofella. Not on my watch.
-[grunts]
-[screams]
[slot machine chiming]
[exhausted panting]
I can't find my way out.
Okay, well, that says
"breakfast buffet" that way,
but I'm pretty sure
we've seen it twice.
♪ ♪
Here we are again
at North Suite Elevators.
I don't know, should we--
should we just
hit the slot machines
while we're here?
No. That's why they do this.
No, no, yeah, no,
I get all that,
and I hate
to hold things up, but...
I mean, Santana's in his 70s.
We should probably see him
while we still can.
Eh.
[guitar solo playing]
[Peter]
I knew one song.
[guitar solo ends]
Son of a bitch.
♪ ♪
There we are. Assembly complete.
So, again, this would be
an appropriate time
for you all to please
log out of the app.
-[Band] Ha! I got you now.
-[gasps]
Mr. Band.
How did you find me?
Honestly, I'm on a guided tour
for the movie The Hangover,
which ends on the roof.
Fun fact, gang--
it was actually Zach's idea
to put the sunglasses
on the baby.
Okay, I see everyone staring
at the Mandalay Bay,
so I'll go ahead and tell you
which window was the shooter's.
Well, you're too late.
In a few moments,
all of Las Vegas will be
totally wiped off the map.
[grunting]
You're a madman.
Why are you doing this?
I need to get out of a very
restrictive time-share deal,
and this is literally
the only way out.
♪ ♪
[Peter]
There was no time.
So that's when I pulled out
Kylo Ren's lightsaber
and knocked Blofella
off the roof.
[screams]
[Quagmire]
No, no, no, no. That's cheating.
[Joe]
Also, you got a lightsaber,
and you're just gonna
push a guy?
[thud]
Oh, triple-five,
you saved my life.
Make love to me right now.
I'm sorry, Alice, I can't.
I'm gay.
New Bond. Edited for snowflakes.
♪ ♪
Wow, that was awesome hearing
about your dream job, Peter.
But I was actually lucky enough
to have my dream job.
At least until I lost it.
It all started years ago.
It was the 1980s,
and I was living alone
in a studio apartment
with an askew poster
because bachelors never hang
their posters straight.
[Peter]
Yeah, no offense, Quagmire,
but I'm gonna listen
to this story
the same way I do
most podcasts--
at 1.5 speed.
[Quagmire, sped up]
I'd put on some weight
from being in an abusive
relationship with a woman--
-Mama Celeste.
-Abbondanza.
[Peter]
All right, okay.
Ba-Back to normal speed.
I-I'm in. I'm hooked.
[Quagmire]
The other thing about
living in the '80s is that,
wherever you went,
the actual Pointer Sisters
would follow you around,
singing.
[tune of "Jump (for My Love)"]
♪ Glenn ♪
♪ You know this man
just mailed a bill ♪
♪ To Sprint ♪
♪ It's for his phone ♪
♪ A landline phone. ♪
[Quagmire]
I knew I needed
to get in shape,
but the only forms of exercise
in the '80s were
roller-skating on a dance floor
or lugging around your dead boss
to use his vacation home.
Back then, there were
two things I liked:
gyrating my pelvis
and putting vowels
next to each other
that weren't normally
next to each other.
I combined those two loves
to create something called
"aerobics."
Welcome aboard.
Here's your
complimentary headband,
two wristbands, waistband,
thigh band, another headband.
There were a lot of bands.
[Peter]
Yeah, my finger's hovering
over that 1.5 button.
[Quagmire]
Yeah, okay, okay, okay.
So I started teaching classes
that same week.
I even created an advanced class
based on how your body moves
during sex.
I called it "Sexercise."
♪ ♪
And things took off immediately
because I gave 1980s women
exactly what they wanted:
long, flat butts.
Come on, ladies.
Longer! Flatter!
My workout program was a hit,
and soon I was ready
to take it national.
I was lucky enough
to get the chance to announce
the filming of my video on
The Tonight Show with Johnny.
[Joe]
Wow! You met Johnny Carson?
[Quagmire]
Actually, that particular night
there was a guest host,
John Davidson,
star of That's Incredible!
So, you know, different Johnny
but still Johnny.
[Peter]
No one has ever called
John Davidson "Johnny."
[Quagmire]
He guest-hosted 87 times.
That's not nothing.
Anyway, the night's first guest
was Jane Fonda,
who was promoting 9 to 5,
by far the blousiest movie
of the 1980s.
So, Glenn Quagmire.
It says here you created
an exercise craze
called "aerobics."
-What inspired that?
-Well, John... ny,
one day as I did jumping jacks
alone in my apartment,
I thought, "How can I take
the worst parts of this
"and put it in a public setting?
Plus a wall of mirrors
and street-facing windows."
The interview seemed
to go great.
But the next day,
I realized how truly ruthless
Jane Fonda was.
♪ ♪
Now, Mr. Quagmire, an important
part of releasing a 1980s video
is the incredibly depressing
production logo it opens with.
I have a few here
to choose from.
First is some vibrating
rainbow text
that never quite comes
into focus.
[ominous synth music playing]
Uh-huh, love that.
This one is just a large
bouncing "V"
with an ominous keyboard noise.
[ominous synth music playing]
Also excellent.
Or here's three capital letters
all spelled with one thick,
continuous line
atop a digital horizon.
[ominous synth music playing]
Wow, you can't miss.
Let's go with all three.
Wait a minute.
What's-what's going on?
Where are my leg warmers?
Back then,
leg warmers were essential
because that was, by far,
the coldest decade
from the knee down.
Did someone take my leg warmers?
In place of my leg warmers,
I found only a single note.
At first, I assumed
Jodie Foster had stolen
my leg warmers,
and I was about to go
take it out on the president.
But then I realized it could
only have been one person intent
on sabotaging me-- Jane Fonda.
I tried my best to soldier on.
Okay, don't look at my legs.
And one, and two...
My calves are tiny and cold.
And three, and four...
But I knew, even in the moment,
it was gonna be a disaster.
[gasping]
I never stood a chance.
♪ ♪
[Jane Fonda]
Hello, Glenn.
Sorry you failed, but...
[chuckles] like they say,
all's fair in love and aerobics.
Who? Who says that? Nobody.
God, now I get why everyone's
racist uncle hates you.
Well, it's been nice chatting,
but if you'll excuse me,
I have to go lobby our nation
about cleaning up the mess
we made in Vietnam.
-[audio speeds up]
-[Peter] Sorry, I went ahead
and hit the eight-X.
[Quagmire]
No, you-you-you did the,
you did the right thing, Peter.
[ominous synth music playing]
♪ ♪
Well, as far as dream jobs go,
mine's always been to do
what you do, Joe, to be a cop.
But, you know, one day
short of retirement,
since y'all got
such a nice benefits package.
Huh. Well, my dream job is to
do pretty much what I do now
but be, like,
a loose cannon type cop
who doesn't care
whether he lives or dies
but can definitely walk.
♪ ♪
[Cleveland]
It was my last day on the job,
and I'd just taken
my last office dump
when I was called
into the chief's office.
Morning, sir.
You wanted to see me?
That's right.
We've been tracking
a notorious drug cartel
that's been bringing
tons of cocaine into L.A.
Yes, cocaine has been ravaging
the Black community for years.
Yeah, well, some white girl
got a minor nosebleed,
so now I guess it's, like,
a big frickin' deal.
In fact, last night,
there was a huge bust.
Wow, how much was it?
And remember,
we measure cocaine--
and nothing else--
in only kilos.
-I don't know, 80 pounds?
-Huh?
Like, 36 kilos.
Oh, my God!
That's too much kilos!
Oh, I'm also assigning you
a new partner.
But don't worry, I know
you're nearing retirement
and want a stable situation,
so I'm hooking you up with a guy
named Sergeant Maniac.
How you doing?
I'm a crazy wild card
as indicated by my
only right now timely mullet.
Hmm. You ain't dressed
like a police detective.
Well, I know we're gonna be
running around chasing bad guys,
so I wore
the tightest jeans I own.
Hi-ya! Hi-ya!
Hey, why don't you come on out
to my beachside trailer
to, uh, discuss the case?
Sure. Where is it?
Eh, not in Malibu--
they wouldn't allow it--
but one of those garbage beaches
further north,
way past Moonshadows, which is,
like, the perfect place
to get drunk and tell everybody
who's responsible
for all the world's wars.
♪ ♪
[Cleveland]
I soon realized my new partner
had serious issues.
He didn't care what kind
of dangerous stuff he did.
-[phone rings]
-Hello?
You're calling from
"credit card services"?
Great, I'll tell you
my Social Security number,
and you tell me if it matches
what you have there.
Man is insane.
Okay, and, uh, don't laugh
at my mother's maiden name.
It's kind of a goofy one.
Tinkleman. [laughing] Yeah.
It's like... like pee.
I thought we were gonna
discuss the case.
Right. I'll be ready
in one minute, but first,
I've been asked to make sure
women come see the movie, too.
♪ ♪
[Cleveland]
So my crazy partner and I
set out to solve the case
and began by looking for Leeds,
which was a somewhat popular
mattress store,
where if you said you were
a potential customer,
they'd let you take a nap
in the middle of the day.
-[snoring]
-Sorry, guys.
My manager says
you have to leave.
Leave? But my partner and I
are trying out this queen bed.
-[giggles]
-What are you giggling at?
We're partners
on the police force.
This guy's wearing jeans
with no underwear.
Yeah, you're cops. Sure.
♪ ♪
You guys are no closer
to figuring out
who's responsible for
bringing in all this cocaine.
I got a pretty good idea.
Have you checked Temple
Shalom Yisrael in Brentwood?
It's also where they control
the weather and the Oscars.
That's it.
You guys are off the case.
♪ ♪
[Cleveland]
Since we'd been thrown off
the case,
I thought it'd be nice
to invite my partner over
-for a home-cooked meal.
-Huh.
You don't have a pitcher
of iced tea?
I thought
every Black family dinner
had a pitcher of iced tea.
We do have a picture of Ice-T,
right up there on the wall.
[dispatcher]
Attention, all units, be advised
of a possible drug deal
at the dock.
That's not far from here.
No way.
We were taken off that case.
Yeah, but we can be there before
even the closest patrol car.
♪ ♪
There, look.
Quick, pull over and let me out.
-What?
-I'm gonna run
the rest of the way.
I assure you the car
will be faster.
See you there.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[panting, grunting]
Been waiting here
for six minutes.
Okay, okay, okay,
so, six-minute mile.
Not bad for jeans
and no underpants.
You got any glovebox Vaseline
in there?
It's the chief. What the hell?
[yells]
The chief has been
the mastermind
of the cocaine cartel all along.
That might explain why
he always calls me at 3:00 a.m.
with screenplay ideas.
[phone ringing]
[grunts] Hello?
[Carter]
Okay, hear me out.
It's Die Hard,
but in a building.
Die Hard is in a building.
Hmm, I don't know.
Here, listen to me watch it,
and we'll find out.
[20th Century Fox fanfare
playing over phone]
[both grunt]
Give it up.
You guys can't arrest me anyway.
I have diplomatic immunity.
-You do?
-On what basis?
Yeah, I'm a citizen
of Margaritaville.
I even have this hat from
a recent vacation to prove it.
[growls] Too bad.
Your diplomatic immunity's
just been revoked.
[groans]
The officer's actions,
while illegal,
were justified by a snappy line.
Movie over.
[ominous synth music playing]
[Quagmire]
I was also a producer
on this project.